experticity.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy | Experticity.com

## Experticity Privacy Policy

Effective Date: 10/07/2015

  * Privacy Policy (US & Multi-Country)
  * EU and Swiss Safe Harbor Statement
  * Privacy Policy (UK & EU)
  * Cookie Policy (UK & EU)
  * Privacy Policy (Canada)
  * Privacy Policy (Australia)
  * Privacy Policy (Korea)
  * Privacy Policy (Hong Kong)
  * POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD (US & Multi-Country)
  * POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDADE (US & Multi-Country)
  * プライバシーポリシー (JP)

## Privacy Policy

  * WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
  * HOW WE USE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
  * SHARING YOUR INFORMATION
  * YOUR CHOICES FOR CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION
  * SECURITY
  * LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
  * CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
  * POLICY CHANGES
  * SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY POLICY

Version:  
United States, Mexico; South Africa; Colombia; Venezuela; Peru; Ecuador; Chile, Uruguay, Brazil; Singapore; Philippines; Indonesia; Malaysia; Thailand; Japan, People’s Republic of China; New Zealand  
Effective Date: 10/07/2015

This privacy policy describes how Experticity, Inc., a company located and incorporated in the United States, collects, uses, and shares information about you that is captured while you use 3point5.com, ProMotive.com or Experticity.com (collectively, “sites”).

By using our sites, registering for our services, or by choosing to submit personal information to Experticity through the sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). You are not required to provide any personal information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to access certain information or areas of the sites. If you do not agree with any terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site or submit any personal information to Experticity.

To the extent identification is required by local law, the data controller is Experticity, Inc.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### All Users

When you visit our sites, we collect personal information about you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, username, and password) (“Personally Identifying Information”) when you fill out forms, communicate with us through our sites, or create an online profile. We may collect personal information that you make publicly available, such as if you make a comment on another user’s content.  

We may also collect certain information about your use of our sites such as information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and your computer’s operating system. Except as otherwise explained in this Policy or as may be prohibited by law, we may combine this information with your personal information.

#### Online Profile

When you create an online profile, you may choose to provide optional information such as your employer, training modules completed, purchases you make, photographs, points earned, etc. Any information you provide on your profile is subject to this Policy. Information you choose to upload or publish to a public area of your profile will appear on the sites, and may be viewed by other members. If you choose to include Personally Identifying Information in a public area of the sites, you consent to the public disclosure of the Personally Identifying Information you choose to post. If you do not wish to publish your Personally Identifying Information in this manner, please do not include it in material you post to a public area of the sites. We provide you ways to control the sharing of your profile, generally, and data within your profile at the following link: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### Cookies and Other Tracking Technology

Our sites also uses “cookies” (small data files stored on your computer) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your visit to our sites. The cookies and tracking technologies we use do not capture Personally Identifying Information. The information that is captured about your visit may be used in a variety of ways, such as to monitor and maintain information about your visits to our sites, to help us identify and address problems, to improve our sites, to analyze web traffic trends, and to help protect the security and integrity of our sites. You may set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you receive cookies, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may still use our sites, but your experience may be degraded.  We may also use pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons,” or “1-by-1gifs”) on our sites. These may be used in connection with certain pages of our sites or with email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, and to assist us in resolving issues that may arise on our site.

### HOW WE USE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

We may use the Personally Identifying Information we collect for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;
  * to send you important information regarding our sites, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, and/or other administrative information;
  * to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, which you may opt-out of at any time;
  * to personalize your experience on our sites by presenting content tailored to you;
  * to allow you to take and keep track of training;
  * for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our sites, improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * for risk control, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements;
  * to use information about your activities on the sites to communicate your progress to your employers and in some cases to offer you retail discounts; and
  * for other purposes which are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

We may also use information that we receive about you from your employer and data providers who assist us in processing requests, maintaining our data, and optimizing our services.

### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We will not disclose your Personally Identifying Information to third parties except as described in this Policy, to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. You agree that we may also disclose this information to third parties: (1) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of our sites, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; or (2) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

We may transfer your Personally Identifying Information to third party service providers that assist us with carrying out these purposes. For example, we may use a data processing contractor to operate computer systems on our behalf, for administrative, technical support, or other business purposes as necessary to facilitate our transactions with you, analyze our data, conduct analytics services, or to maintain and improve our services. Whenever any Personally Identifying Information is transferred to a such a third party service provider, that party will be contractually bound to use such Personally Identifying Information only to carry out the services we have requested, to abide by our Policy, and to provide adequate protection for the Personally Identifying Information.

We reserve the right to transfer any Personally Identifying Information we have about you in the event that we merge with or are acquired by a third party. We may disclose your Personally Identifying Information for any other purpose with your consent.

### YOUR CHOICES FOR CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION

#### Correcting or Changing Your Information

We are concerned about the accuracy, currency, and completeness of the Personally Identifying Information we collect and take appropriate steps to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. In addition to the options provided to you in this Policy, if you wish to review, amend, correct, update, or delete Personally Identifying Information we have collected about you online, or to opt out of receiving our marketing communications, contact us at: +1-866-376-4685 or http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback. You may also contact us by writing to:

Ron Martinez  
Experticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

We will respond to your access request within any legally required time period or within 30 days. We reserve the right not to allow access to your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is prohibited by law or if the rights of another individual might be violated.

You may cancel your registration to our sites and/or request the removal of your Personally Identifying Information from our visitor records by sending an email at http://www.3point5.com/feedback. We will send an email to confirm your request. After you respond, we will remove your information from our database. Residual information may remain in our archives and records, but this information will not be used for any purpose, commercial or otherwise. We reserve the right to maintain information on registered visitors who have violated any of our policies or who have had their access to the site blocked.

### SECURITY

We use a variety of technologies and processes to protect Personally Identifying Information collected on the sites, including physical, technological, and organizational security measures. For example, we use encryption technology whenever transmitting personal information. Unfortunately, no security technology is completely secure, and you should remember that email is not a secure means of communication. We retain Personally Identifying Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to meet any legal requirements.

Some or all of the Personally Identifying Information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside of your country, including in the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from those where you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personally Identifying Information that are equivalent to those in your country.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our sites may contain links to websites owned by third parties. Information you share with a third party site is not subject to this Policy. Please review the privacy policy of any sites you access through our sites.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our sites are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from creating an online profile.

### POLICY CHANGES

If our Policy changes, we will post these changes to our sites with the date of revision. We encourage you to review our Policy periodically.  Your continued access to and/or use of the sites after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of, and agreement to be legally bound by, this Policy, as revised. If our privacy practices, including the ways we use your Personally Identifying Information, materially change from the time you created an online profile, we will notify you about such changes before they take effect and allow you to delete your information as described above, should you disagree with such changes.

## Safe Harbor Privacy Policy

Experticity, Inc. (“Experticity”), as part of this Policy, complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Experticity has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Experticity’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

In compliance with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Experticity commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Experticity Member Services at: 866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>.

Experticity has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Experticity, please visit the BBB E.U. SAFE HARBOR website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Version: United Kingdom & European Union  
Effective Date: 10/07/2015

This privacy policy describes how Experticity, Inc., a company located and incorporated in the United States, collects, uses, and shares information about you that is captured while you use 3point5.com, ProMotive.com or Experticity.com (collectively, “sites”).

By using our sites, registering for our services, or by choosing to submit personal information to Experticity through the sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). You are not required to provide any personal information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to access certain information or areas of the sites. If you do not agree with any terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site or submit any personal information to Experticity.

To the extent identification is required by local law, the data controller is Experticity, Inc.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### All Users

When you visit our sites, we collect personal information about you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, username, and password) (“Personally Identifying Information”) when you fill out forms, communicate with us through our sites, or create an online profile. We may collect personal information that you make publicly available, such as if you make a comment on another user’s content. 

We may also collect certain information about your use of our sites such as information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and your computer’s operating system. Except as otherwise explained in this Policy or as may be prohibited by law, we may combine this information with your personal information.

#### Online Profile

When you create an online profile, you may choose to provide optional information such as your employer, training modules completed, purchases you make, photographs, points earned, etc. Any information you provide on your profile is subject to this Policy. Information you choose to upload or publish to a public area of your profile will appear on the sites, and may be viewed by other members. If you choose to include Personally Identifying Information in a public area of the sites, you consent to the public disclosure of the Personally Identifying Information you choose to post. If you do not wish to publish your Personally Identifying Information in this manner, please do not include it in material you post to a public area of the sites. We provide you ways to control the sharing of your profile, generally, and data within your profile at the following link: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

Our sites also uses “cookies” (small data files stored on your computer) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your visit to our sites. The cookies and tracking technologies we use do not capture Personally Identifying Information. The information that is captured about your visit may be used in a variety of ways, such as to monitor and maintain information about your visits to our sites, to help us identify and address problems, to improve our sites, to analyze web traffic trends, and to help protect the security and integrity of our sites. You may set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you receive cookies, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may still use our sites, but your experience may be degraded. We may also use pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons,” or “1-by-1gifs”) on our sites. These may be used in connection with certain pages of our sites or with email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, and to assist us in resolving issues that may arise on our site.

#### HOW WE USE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

We may use the Personally Identifying Information we collect for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;
  * to send you important information regarding our site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, and/or other administrative information;
  * to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, if you have agreed to receive such messages;
  * to personalize your experience on our site by presenting content tailored to you;
  * to allow you to take and keep track of training;
  * for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our site, improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * for risk control, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements;
  * to use information about your activities on the site to communicate your training progress to your employers and in some cases to offer you retail discounts;
  * for other purposes which are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

We may also use information that we receive about you from your employer and data providers who assist us in processing requests, maintaining our data, and optimizing our services.

### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We will not disclose your Personally Identifying Information to third parties except as described in this Policy, to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. You agree that we may also disclose this information to third parties: (1) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of our sites, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; or (2) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

We may transfer your Personally Identifying Information to third party service providers that assist us with carrying out these purposes. For example, we may use a data processing contractor to operate computer systems on our behalf, for administrative, technical support, or other business purposes as necessary to facilitate our transactions with you, analyze our data, conduct analytics services, or to maintain and improve our services. Whenever any Personally Identifying Information is transferred to a such a third party service provider, that party will be contractually bound to use such Personally Identifying Information only to carry out the services we have requested, to abide by our Policy, and to provide adequate protection for the Personally Identifying Information.

We reserve the right to transfer any Personally Identifying Information we have about you in the event that we merge with or are acquired by a third party. We may disclose your Personally Identifying Information for any other purpose with your consent.

### YOUR CHOICES FOR CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION

#### Correcting or Changing Your Information

We are concerned about the accuracy, currency, and completeness of the Personally Identifying Information we collect and take appropriate steps to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. In addition to the options provided to you in this Policy, if you wish to review, amend, correct, update, or delete Personally Identifying Information we have collected about you online, or to opt out of receiving our marketing communications, contact us at: +1-866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>. You may also contact us by writing to:

Ron Martinez  
Experticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

We will respond to your access request within any legally required time period or within 30 days. We reserve the right not to allow access to your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is prohibited by law or if the rights of another individual might be violated.

You may cancel your registration to our sites and/or request the removal of your Personally Identifying Information from our visitor records by sending an email at http://www.3point5.com/feedback. We will send an email to confirm your request. After you respond, we will remove your information from our database. Residual information may remain in our archives and records, but this information will not be used for any purpose, commercial or otherwise. We reserve the right to maintain information on registered visitors who have violated any of our policies or who have had their access to the site blocked.

### SECURITY

We use a variety of technologies and processes to protect Personally Identifying Information collected on the sites, including physical, technological, and organizational security measures. For example, we use encryption technology whenever transmitting personal information. Unfortunately, no security technology is completely secure, and you should remember that email is not a secure means of communication. We retain Personally Identifying Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to meet any legal requirements.

Some or all of the Personally Identifying Information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside of your country, including in the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from those where you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personally Identifying Information that are equivalent to those in your country.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our sites may contain links to websites owned by third parties. Information you share with a third party site is not subject to this Policy. Please review the privacy policy of any sites you access through our sites.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our sites are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from creating an online profile.

### POLICY CHANGES

If our Policy changes, we will post these changes to our sites with the date of revision. We encourage you to review our Policy periodically. Your continued access to and/or use of the sites after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of, and agreement to be legally bound by, this Policy, as revised. If our privacy practices, including the ways we use your Personally Identifying Information, materially change from the time you created an online profile, we will notify you about such changes before they take effect and allow you to delete your information as described above, should you disagree with such changes.

### SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY POLICY

Experticity, Inc. (“Experticity”), as part of this Policy, complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Experticity has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Experticity’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.  
In compliance with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Experticity commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Experticity Member Services at: 866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>.  
Experticity has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Experticity, please visit the BBB E.U. SAFE HARBOR website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint. 

## PRIVACY POLICY

Version: Canada  
Effective Date: 10/07/2015

This privacy policy describes how Experticity, Inc., a company located and incorporated in the United States, collects, uses, and shares information about you that is captured while you use 3point5.com, ProMotive.com or Experticity.com (collectively, “sites”).

By using our sites, registering for our services, or by choosing to submit personal information to Experticity through the sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). You are not required to provide any personal information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to access certain information or areas of the sites. If you do not agree with any terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site or submit any personal information to Experticity.

To the extent identification is required by local law, the data controller is Experticity, Inc.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### All Users

When you visit our sites, we collect personal information about you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, username, and password) (“Personally Identifying Information”) when you fill out forms, communicate with us through our sites, or create an online profile. We may collect personal information that you make publicly available, such as if you make a comment on another user’s content. 

We may also collect certain information about your use of our sites such as information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and your computer’s operating system. Except as otherwise explained in this Policy or as may be prohibited by law, we may combine this information with your personal information.

#### Online Profile

When you create an online profile, you may choose to provide optional information such as your employer, training modules completed, purchases you make, photographs, points earned, etc. Any information you provide on your profile is subject to this Policy. Information you choose to upload or publish to a public area of your profile will appear on the sites, and may be viewed by other members. If you choose to include Personally Identifying Information in a public area of the sites, you consent to the public disclosure of the Personally Identifying Information you choose to post. If you do not wish to publish your Personally Identifying Information in this manner, please do not include it in material you post to a public area of the sites. We provide you ways to control the sharing of your profile, generally, and data within your profile at the following link: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

Our sites also uses “cookies” (small data files stored on your computer) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your visit to our sites. The cookies and tracking technologies we use do not capture Personally Identifying Information. The information that is captured about your visit may be used in a variety of ways, such as to monitor and maintain information about your visits to our sites, to help us identify and address problems, to improve our sites, to analyze web traffic trends, and to help protect the security and integrity of our sites. You may set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you receive cookies, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may still use our sites, but your experience may be degraded. We may also use pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons,” or “1-by-1gifs”) on our sites. These may be used in connection with certain pages of our sites or with email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, and to assist us in resolving issues that may arise on our site.

#### HOW WE USE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

We may use the Personally Identifying Information we collect for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;
  * to send you important information regarding our site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, and/or other administrative information;
  * to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, if you have agreed to receive such messages;
  * to personalize your experience on our site by presenting content tailored to you;
  * to allow you to take and keep track of training;
  * for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our site, improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * for risk control, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements;
  * to use information about your activities on the site to communicate your training progress to your employers and in some cases to offer you retail discounts;
  * for other purposes which are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

We may also use information that we receive about you from your employer and data providers who assist us in processing requests, maintaining our data, and optimizing our services.

### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We will not disclose your Personally Identifying Information to third parties except as described in this Policy, to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. You agree that we may also disclose this information to third parties: (1) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of our sites, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; or (2) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

We may transfer your Personally Identifying Information to third party service providers that assist us with carrying out these purposes. For example, we may use a data processing contractor to operate computer systems on our behalf, for administrative, technical support, or other business purposes as necessary to facilitate our transactions with you, analyze our data, conduct analytics services, or to maintain and improve our services. Whenever any Personally Identifying Information is transferred to a such a third party service provider, that party will be contractually bound to use such Personally Identifying Information only to carry out the services we have requested, to abide by our Policy, and to provide adequate protection for the Personally Identifying Information.

We reserve the right to transfer any Personally Identifying Information we have about you in the event that we merge with or are acquired by a third party. We may disclose your Personally Identifying Information for any other purpose with your consent.

### YOUR CHOICES FOR CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION

#### Correcting or Changing Your Information

We are concerned about the accuracy, currency, and completeness of the Personally Identifying Information we collect and take appropriate steps to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. In addition to the options provided to you in this Policy, if you wish to review, amend, correct, update, or delete Personally Identifying Information we have collected about you online, or to opt out of receiving our marketing communications, contact us at: +1-866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>. You may also contact us by writing to:

Ron Martinez  
Experticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

We will respond to your access request within any legally required time period or within 30 days. We reserve the right not to allow access to your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is prohibited by law or if the rights of another individual might be violated.

You may cancel your registration to our sites and/or request the removal of your Personally Identifying Information from our visitor records by sending an email at http://www.3point5.com/feedback. We will send an email to confirm your request. After you respond, we will remove your information from our database. Residual information may remain in our archives and records, but this information will not be used for any purpose, commercial or otherwise. We reserve the right to maintain information on registered visitors who have violated any of our policies or who have had their access to the site blocked.

### SECURITY

We use a variety of technologies and processes to protect Personally Identifying Information collected on the sites, including physical, technological, and organizational security measures. For example, we use encryption technology whenever transmitting personal information. Unfortunately, no security technology is completely secure, and you should remember that email is not a secure means of communication. We retain Personally Identifying Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to meet any legal requirements.

Some or all of the Personally Identifying Information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside of your country, including in the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from those where you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personally Identifying Information that are equivalent to those in your country.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our sites may contain links to websites owned by third parties. Information you share with a third party site is not subject to this Policy. Please review the privacy policy of any sites you access through our sites.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our sites are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from creating an online profile.

### POLICY CHANGES

If our Policy changes, we will post these changes to our sites with the date of revision. We encourage you to review our Policy periodically. Your continued access to and/or use of the sites after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of, and agreement to be legally bound by, this Policy, as revised. If our privacy practices, including the ways we use your Personally Identifying Information, materially change from the time you created an online profile, we will notify you about such changes before they take effect and allow you to delete your information as described above, should you disagree with such changes.

### SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY POLICY

Experticity, Inc. (“Experticity”), as part of this Policy, complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Experticity has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Experticity’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.  
In compliance with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Experticity commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Experticity Member Services at: 866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>.  
Experticity has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Experticity, please visit the BBB E.U. SAFE HARBOR website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Version: Australia  
Effective Date: 10/07/2015

This privacy policy describes how Experticity, Inc., a company located and incorporated in the United States, collects, uses, and shares information about you that is captured while you use 3point5.com, ProMotive.com or Experticity.com (collectively, “sites”).

By using our sites, registering for our services, or by choosing to submit personal information to Experticity through the sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). You are not required to provide any personal information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to access certain information or areas of the sites. If you do not agree with any terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site or submit any personal information to Experticity.

To the extent identification is required by local law, the data controller is Experticity, Inc.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### All Users

When you visit our sites, we collect personal information about you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, username, and password) (“Personally Identifying Information”) when you fill out forms, communicate with us through our sites, or create an online profile. We may collect personal information that you make publicly available, such as if you make a comment on another user’s content. 

We may also collect certain information about your use of our sites such as information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and your computer’s operating system. Except as otherwise explained in this Policy or as may be prohibited by law, we may combine this information with your personal information.

#### Online Profile

When you create an online profile, you may choose to provide optional information such as your employer, training modules completed, purchases you make, photographs, points earned, etc. Any information you provide on your profile is subject to this Policy. Information you choose to upload or publish to a public area of your profile will appear on the sites, and may be viewed by other members. If you choose to include Personally Identifying Information in a public area of the sites, you consent to the public disclosure of the Personally Identifying Information you choose to post. If you do not wish to publish your Personally Identifying Information in this manner, please do not include it in material you post to a public area of the sites. We provide you ways to control the sharing of your profile, generally, and data within your profile at the following link: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

Our sites also uses “cookies” (small data files stored on your computer) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your visit to our sites. The cookies and tracking technologies we use do not capture Personally Identifying Information. The information that is captured about your visit may be used in a variety of ways, such as to monitor and maintain information about your visits to our sites, to help us identify and address problems, to improve our sites, to analyze web traffic trends, and to help protect the security and integrity of our sites. You may set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you receive cookies, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may still use our sites, but your experience may be degraded. We may also use pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons,” or “1-by-1gifs”) on our sites. These may be used in connection with certain pages of our sites or with email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, and to assist us in resolving issues that may arise on our site.

#### HOW WE USE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

We may use the Personally Identifying Information we collect for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;
  * to send you important information regarding our site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, and/or other administrative information;
  * to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, if you have agreed to receive such messages;
  * to personalize your experience on our site by presenting content tailored to you;
  * to allow you to take and keep track of training;
  * for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our site, improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * for risk control, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements;
  * to use information about your activities on the site to communicate your training progress to your employers and in some cases to offer you retail discounts;
  * for other purposes which are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

We may also use information that we receive about you from your employer and data providers who assist us in processing requests, maintaining our data, and optimizing our services.

### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We will not disclose your Personally Identifying Information to third parties except as described in this Policy, to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. You agree that we may also disclose this information to third parties: (1) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of our sites, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; or (2) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

We may transfer your Personally Identifying Information to third party service providers that assist us with carrying out these purposes. For example, we may use a data processing contractor to operate computer systems on our behalf, for administrative, technical support, or other business purposes as necessary to facilitate our transactions with you, analyze our data, conduct analytics services, or to maintain and improve our services. Whenever any Personally Identifying Information is transferred to a such a third party service provider, that party will be contractually bound to use such Personally Identifying Information only to carry out the services we have requested, to abide by our Policy, and to provide adequate protection for the Personally Identifying Information.

We reserve the right to transfer any Personally Identifying Information we have about you in the event that we merge with or are acquired by a third party. We may disclose your Personally Identifying Information for any other purpose with your consent.

### YOUR CHOICES FOR CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION

#### Correcting or Changing Your Information

We are concerned about the accuracy, currency, and completeness of the Personally Identifying Information we collect and take appropriate steps to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. In addition to the options provided to you in this Policy, if you wish to review, amend, correct, update, or delete Personally Identifying Information we have collected about you online, or to opt out of receiving our marketing communications, contact us at: +1-866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>. You may also contact us by writing to:

Ron Martinez  
Experticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

We will respond to your access request within any legally required time period or within 30 days. We reserve the right not to allow access to your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is prohibited by law or if the rights of another individual might be violated.

You may cancel your registration to our sites and/or request the removal of your Personally Identifying Information from our visitor records by sending an email at http://www.3point5.com/feedback. We will send an email to confirm your request. After you respond, we will remove your information from our database. Residual information may remain in our archives and records, but this information will not be used for any purpose, commercial or otherwise. We reserve the right to maintain information on registered visitors who have violated any of our policies or who have had their access to the site blocked.

### SECURITY

We use a variety of technologies and processes to protect Personally Identifying Information collected on the sites, including physical, technological, and organizational security measures. For example, we use encryption technology whenever transmitting personal information. Unfortunately, no security technology is completely secure, and you should remember that email is not a secure means of communication. We retain Personally Identifying Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to meet any legal requirements.

Some or all of the Personally Identifying Information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside of your country, including in the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from those where you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personally Identifying Information that are equivalent to those in your country.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our sites may contain links to websites owned by third parties. Information you share with a third party site is not subject to this Policy. Please review the privacy policy of any sites you access through our sites.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our sites are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from creating an online profile.

### POLICY CHANGES

If our Policy changes, we will post these changes to our sites with the date of revision. We encourage you to review our Policy periodically. Your continued access to and/or use of the sites after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of, and agreement to be legally bound by, this Policy, as revised. If our privacy practices, including the ways we use your Personally Identifying Information, materially change from the time you created an online profile, we will notify you about such changes before they take effect and allow you to delete your information as described above, should you disagree with such changes.

### SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY POLICY

Experticity, Inc. (“Experticity”), as part of this Policy, complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Experticity has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Experticity’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.  
In compliance with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Experticity commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Experticity Member Services at: 866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>.  
Experticity has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Experticity, please visit the BBB E.U. SAFE HARBOR website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Version: South Korea  
Effective Date: 10/07/2015

This privacy policy describes how Experticity, Inc., a company located and incorporated in the United States, collects, uses, and shares information about you that is captured while you use 3point5.com, ProMotive.com or Experticity.com (collectively, “sites”).

By using our sites, registering for our services, or by choosing to submit personal information to Experticity through the sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). You are not required to provide any personal information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to access certain information or areas of the sites. If you do not agree with any terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site or submit any personal information to Experticity.

To the extent identification is required by local law, the data controller is Experticity, Inc.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### All Users

When you visit our sites, we collect personal information about you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, username, and password) (“Personally Identifying Information”) when you fill out forms, communicate with us through our sites, or create an online profile. We may collect personal information that you make publicly available, such as if you make a comment on another user’s content. 

We may also collect certain information about your use of our sites such as information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and your computer’s operating system. Except as otherwise explained in this Policy or as may be prohibited by law, we may combine this information with your personal information.

#### Online Profile

When you create an online profile, you may choose to provide optional information such as your employer, training modules completed, purchases you make, photographs, points earned, etc. Any information you provide on your profile is subject to this Policy. Information you choose to upload or publish to a public area of your profile will appear on the sites, and may be viewed by other members. If you choose to include Personally Identifying Information in a public area of the sites, you consent to the public disclosure of the Personally Identifying Information you choose to post. If you do not wish to publish your Personally Identifying Information in this manner, please do not include it in material you post to a public area of the sites. We provide you ways to control the sharing of your profile, generally, and data within your profile at the following link: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

Our sites also uses “cookies” (small data files stored on your computer) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your visit to our sites. The cookies and tracking technologies we use do not capture Personally Identifying Information. The information that is captured about your visit may be used in a variety of ways, such as to monitor and maintain information about your visits to our sites, to help us identify and address problems, to improve our sites, to analyze web traffic trends, and to help protect the security and integrity of our sites. You may set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you receive cookies, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may still use our sites, but your experience may be degraded. We may also use pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons,” or “1-by-1gifs”) on our sites. These may be used in connection with certain pages of our sites or with email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, and to assist us in resolving issues that may arise on our site.

#### HOW WE USE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

We may use the Personally Identifying Information we collect for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;
  * to send you important information regarding our site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, and/or other administrative information;
  * to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, if you have agreed to receive such messages;
  * to personalize your experience on our site by presenting content tailored to you;
  * to allow you to take and keep track of training;
  * for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our site, improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * for risk control, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements;
  * to use information about your activities on the site to communicate your training progress to your employers and in some cases to offer you retail discounts;
  * for other purposes which are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

We may also use information that we receive about you from your employer and data providers who assist us in processing requests, maintaining our data, and optimizing our services.

### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We will not disclose your Personally Identifying Information to third parties except as described in this Policy, to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. You agree that we may also disclose this information to third parties: (1) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of our sites, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; or (2) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

We may transfer your Personally Identifying Information to third party service providers that assist us with carrying out these purposes. For example, we may use a data processing contractor to operate computer systems on our behalf, for administrative, technical support, or other business purposes as necessary to facilitate our transactions with you, analyze our data, conduct analytics services, or to maintain and improve our services. Whenever any Personally Identifying Information is transferred to a such a third party service provider, that party will be contractually bound to use such Personally Identifying Information only to carry out the services we have requested, to abide by our Policy, and to provide adequate protection for the Personally Identifying Information.

We reserve the right to transfer any Personally Identifying Information we have about you in the event that we merge with or are acquired by a third party. We may disclose your Personally Identifying Information for any other purpose with your consent.

### YOUR CHOICES FOR CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION

#### Correcting or Changing Your Information

We are concerned about the accuracy, currency, and completeness of the Personally Identifying Information we collect and take appropriate steps to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. In addition to the options provided to you in this Policy, if you wish to review, amend, correct, update, or delete Personally Identifying Information we have collected about you online, or to opt out of receiving our marketing communications, contact us at: +1-866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>. You may also contact us by writing to:

Ron Martinez  
Experticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

We will respond to your access request within any legally required time period or within 30 days. We reserve the right not to allow access to your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is prohibited by law or if the rights of another individual might be violated.

You may cancel your registration to our sites and/or request the removal of your Personally Identifying Information from our visitor records by sending an email at http://www.3point5.com/feedback. We will send an email to confirm your request. After you respond, we will remove your information from our database. Residual information may remain in our archives and records, but this information will not be used for any purpose, commercial or otherwise. We reserve the right to maintain information on registered visitors who have violated any of our policies or who have had their access to the site blocked.

### SECURITY

We use a variety of technologies and processes to protect Personally Identifying Information collected on the sites, including physical, technological, and organizational security measures. For example, we use encryption technology whenever transmitting personal information. Unfortunately, no security technology is completely secure, and you should remember that email is not a secure means of communication. We retain Personally Identifying Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to meet any legal requirements.

Some or all of the Personally Identifying Information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside of your country, including in the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from those where you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personally Identifying Information that are equivalent to those in your country.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our sites may contain links to websites owned by third parties. Information you share with a third party site is not subject to this Policy. Please review the privacy policy of any sites you access through our sites.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our sites are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from creating an online profile.

### POLICY CHANGES

If our Policy changes, we will post these changes to our sites with the date of revision. We encourage you to review our Policy periodically. Your continued access to and/or use of the sites after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of, and agreement to be legally bound by, this Policy, as revised. If our privacy practices, including the ways we use your Personally Identifying Information, materially change from the time you created an online profile, we will notify you about such changes before they take effect and allow you to delete your information as described above, should you disagree with such changes.

### SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY POLICY

Experticity, Inc. (“Experticity”), as part of this Policy, complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Experticity has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Experticity’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.  
In compliance with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Experticity commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Experticity Member Services at: 866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>.  
Experticity has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Experticity, please visit the BBB E.U. SAFE HARBOR website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Version: Hong Kong  
Effective Date: 10/07/2015

This privacy policy describes how Experticity, Inc., a company located and incorporated in the United States, collects, uses, and shares information about you that is captured while you use 3point5.com, ProMotive.com or Experticity.com (collectively, “sites”).

By using our sites, registering for our services, or by choosing to submit personal information to Experticity through the sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). You are not required to provide any personal information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to access certain information or areas of the sites. If you do not agree with any terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site or submit any personal information to Experticity.

To the extent identification is required by local law, the data controller is Experticity, Inc.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### All Users

When you visit our sites, we collect personal information about you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, username, and password) (“Personally Identifying Information”) when you fill out forms, communicate with us through our sites, or create an online profile. We may collect personal information that you make publicly available, such as if you make a comment on another user’s content. 

We may also collect certain information about your use of our sites such as information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and your computer’s operating system. Except as otherwise explained in this Policy or as may be prohibited by law, we may combine this information with your personal information.

#### Online Profile

When you create an online profile, you may choose to provide optional information such as your employer, training modules completed, purchases you make, photographs, points earned, etc. Any information you provide on your profile is subject to this Policy. Information you choose to upload or publish to a public area of your profile will appear on the sites, and may be viewed by other members. If you choose to include Personally Identifying Information in a public area of the sites, you consent to the public disclosure of the Personally Identifying Information you choose to post. If you do not wish to publish your Personally Identifying Information in this manner, please do not include it in material you post to a public area of the sites. We provide you ways to control the sharing of your profile, generally, and data within your profile at the following link: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

Our sites also uses “cookies” (small data files stored on your computer) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your visit to our sites. The cookies and tracking technologies we use do not capture Personally Identifying Information. The information that is captured about your visit may be used in a variety of ways, such as to monitor and maintain information about your visits to our sites, to help us identify and address problems, to improve our sites, to analyze web traffic trends, and to help protect the security and integrity of our sites. You may set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you receive cookies, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may still use our sites, but your experience may be degraded. We may also use pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons,” or “1-by-1gifs”) on our sites. These may be used in connection with certain pages of our sites or with email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, and to assist us in resolving issues that may arise on our site.

#### HOW WE USE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

We may use the Personally Identifying Information we collect for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;
  * to send you important information regarding our site, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, and/or other administrative information;
  * to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, if you have agreed to receive such messages;
  * to personalize your experience on our site by presenting content tailored to you;
  * to allow you to take and keep track of training;
  * for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our site, improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * for risk control, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements;
  * to use information about your activities on the site to communicate your training progress to your employers and in some cases to offer you retail discounts;
  * for other purposes which are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

We may also use information that we receive about you from your employer and data providers who assist us in processing requests, maintaining our data, and optimizing our services.

### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We will not disclose your Personally Identifying Information to third parties except as described in this Policy, to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. You agree that we may also disclose this information to third parties: (1) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of our sites, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; or (2) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

We may transfer your Personally Identifying Information to third party service providers that assist us with carrying out these purposes. For example, we may use a data processing contractor to operate computer systems on our behalf, for administrative, technical support, or other business purposes as necessary to facilitate our transactions with you, analyze our data, conduct analytics services, or to maintain and improve our services. Whenever any Personally Identifying Information is transferred to a such a third party service provider, that party will be contractually bound to use such Personally Identifying Information only to carry out the services we have requested, to abide by our Policy, and to provide adequate protection for the Personally Identifying Information.

We reserve the right to transfer any Personally Identifying Information we have about you in the event that we merge with or are acquired by a third party. We may disclose your Personally Identifying Information for any other purpose with your consent.

### YOUR CHOICES FOR CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION

#### Correcting or Changing Your Information

We are concerned about the accuracy, currency, and completeness of the Personally Identifying Information we collect and take appropriate steps to ensure that the information we have is accurate and up-to-date. In addition to the options provided to you in this Policy, if you wish to review, amend, correct, update, or delete Personally Identifying Information we have collected about you online, or to opt out of receiving our marketing communications, contact us at: +1-866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>. You may also contact us by writing to:

Ron Martinez  
Experticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

We will respond to your access request within any legally required time period or within 30 days. We reserve the right not to allow access to your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is prohibited by law or if the rights of another individual might be violated.

You may cancel your registration to our sites and/or request the removal of your Personally Identifying Information from our visitor records by sending an email at http://www.3point5.com/feedback. We will send an email to confirm your request. After you respond, we will remove your information from our database. Residual information may remain in our archives and records, but this information will not be used for any purpose, commercial or otherwise. We reserve the right to maintain information on registered visitors who have violated any of our policies or who have had their access to the site blocked.

### SECURITY

We use a variety of technologies and processes to protect Personally Identifying Information collected on the sites, including physical, technological, and organizational security measures. For example, we use encryption technology whenever transmitting personal information. Unfortunately, no security technology is completely secure, and you should remember that email is not a secure means of communication. We retain Personally Identifying Information that we collect only as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or to meet any legal requirements.

Some or all of the Personally Identifying Information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located outside of your country, including in the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from those where you live. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Subject to applicable laws in such other jurisdictions, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that appropriate protections are in place to maintain protections on the Personally Identifying Information that are equivalent to those in your country.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our sites may contain links to websites owned by third parties. Information you share with a third party site is not subject to this Policy. Please review the privacy policy of any sites you access through our sites.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our sites are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from creating an online profile.

### POLICY CHANGES

If our Policy changes, we will post these changes to our sites with the date of revision. We encourage you to review our Policy periodically. Your continued access to and/or use of the sites after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of, and agreement to be legally bound by, this Policy, as revised. If our privacy practices, including the ways we use your Personally Identifying Information, materially change from the time you created an online profile, we will notify you about such changes before they take effect and allow you to delete your information as described above, should you disagree with such changes.

### SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY POLICY

Experticity, Inc. (“Experticity”), as part of this Policy, complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Experticity has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Experticity’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.  
In compliance with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Experticity commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Experticity Member Services at: 866-376-4685 or <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>.  
Experticity has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principles and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Experticity, please visit the BBB E.U. SAFE HARBOR website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint.

## POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD

Versión: Estados Unidos, México; Sudáfrica; Colombia; Venezuela; Perú; Ecuador; Chile, Uruguay, Brasil; Singapur; Filipinas; Indonesia; Malasia; Tailandia; Japón, República Popular de China; Nueva Zelanda  
Fecha de entrada en vigor: 10/07/2015

Esta política de privacidad describe el modo en que eXperticity, Inc., una compañía constituida y con domicilio en los Estados Unidos, recopila, utiliza y comparte información sobre usted, la cual se obtiene mientras usted hace uso de 3point5.com (el “Sitio”).

Al utilizar nuestro sitio, registrarse para recibir nuestros servicios u optar por enviar información personal a eXperticity a través del sitio, usted acepta los términos de esta Política de privacidad (la “Política”). No se le exige proporcionar información personal pero, si es usted el que opta por no hacerlo, es posible que no pueda tener acceso a determinada información o áreas del sitio. Si no está de acuerdo con los términos de esta Política, no haga uso de este Sitio ni envíe información personal a eXperticity.

En la medida en que la legislación local presente exigencias en cuanto a la identificación, el controlador de datos es eXperticity, Inc.

### QUÉ TIPO DE INFORMACIÓN SE RECOPILA

#### Todos los usuarios

Cuando visita nuestro sitio, recopilamos información personal sobre usted (que incluye nombre, dirección, número de teléfono, dirección electrónica, nombre de usuario, contraseña) (“Información de identificación personal”) mientras completa formularios, se comunica con nosotros a través de nuestro sitio o crea un perfil por Internet.

También recopilamos determinada información sobre el uso que hace de nuestro sitio, como información sobre su equipo, que incluye su dirección IP, el tipo de navegador que utiliza y el sistema operativo de su equipo informático. Salvo que se establezca lo contrario en esta Política, o según lo prohíba la ley, es posible que combinemos esta información con su información personal.

#### Perfil por Internet

Cuando crea un perfil por Internet, puede elegir brindar información optativa, como su empleador, módulos de capacitación realizados, compras que haya realizado, fotografías, puntos ganados, etc. Toda información que proporcione en su perfil queda sujeta a esta Política. La información que opte por cargar o publicar en una sección pública de su perfil aparecerá en el sitio y puede ser vista por los demás miembros. Si opta por incluir Información de identificación personal en una sección pública del sitio, admite que está de acuerdo con la divulgación pública de la Información de identificación personal que elige publicar. Si no desea publicar su Información de identificación personal de esta manera, tenga a bien no incluirla en el material que divulgue en una sección pública de este sitio. Le proporcionamos maneras para que controle la divulgación de su perfil, en general, y los datos dentro de su perfil. Visite el siguiente enlace: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### Cookies y demás tecnologías de rastreo

Nuestro sitio, además, utiliza “cookies” (pequeños archivos de datos que se almacenan en su equipo informático) y otros elementos tecnológicos de rastreo a fin de recabar información sobre su visita a nuestro sitio. Las cookies y las tecnologías de rastreo que utilizamos no captan Información de identificación personal. La información que se obtiene sobre su visita puede utilizarse en una variedad de maneras, como para supervisar y conservar información sobre sus visitas a nuestro sitio, ayudarnos a identificar y abordar problemas, mejorar nuestro sitio, analizar las tendencias del tráfico virtual y ayudarnos a proteger la seguridad e integridad de nuestro sitio. Puede configurar su navegador para que no acepte cookies o le notifique cuando reciba cookies, lo que le da la oportunidad de decidir si aceptarlas o no. Si no acepta las cookies, es posible que aún pueda utilizar nuestro sitio; sin embargo, su experiencia puede verse disminuida.

Es posible que también utilicemos etiquetas de píxeles (también conocidas como “gifs transparentes”, “balizas web” o “1 x 1 gifs”) en nuestro sitio. Estas pueden utilizarse en relación con ciertas páginas de nuestro sitio o con los mensajes de correo electrónico para medir la efectividad de nuestras comunicaciones y campañas de comercialización, a fin de compilar estadísticas sobre el uso y los índices de respuesta, y para tener ayuda al resolver problemas que puedan surgir en nuestro sitio.

### CÓMO USAMOS LA INFORMACIÓN DE IDENTIFICACIÓN PERSONAL RECOPILADA

Es posible que utilicemos la Información de identificación personal que recopilemos con los siguientes objetivos:

  * para responder a sus preguntas y solicitudes;
  * para enviarle información importante sobre nuestro sitio, cambios en los términos, las condiciones y las políticas, y demás información administrativa;
  * para enviarle comunicaciones de comercialización que creemos que pueden interesarle, las cuales puede dejar de recibir en cualquier momento;
  * para personalizar su experiencia en nuestro sitio, mediante la presentación de contenido que se adecue a usted;
  * para permitirle hacer un seguimiento de la capacitación;
  * para responder a nuestros fines comerciales, como el análisis de datos, las auditorías, el desarrollo de productos nuevos, las mejoras a nuestro sitio y nuestros servicios, la identificación de tendencias de uso y la determinación de la efectividad de nuestras campañas promocionales;
  * para el control de riesgos, el cumplimiento de las leyes y normas, y demás requisitos de procesamiento legal y exigibilidad de las leyes;
  * para utilizar información sobre sus actividades en el sitio, a fin de comunicar su progreso a sus empleadores y, en algunos casos, ofrecerle descuentos al por menor;
  * para otros fines que se divulguen, los cuales acepte.

Es posible que también usemos información sobre usted que recibamos de su empleador y proveedores de información, quienes nos ayudan a procesar solicitudes, conservar nuestra información y optimizar nuestros servicios.

#### DIVULGACIÓN DE LA INFORMACIÓN

No divulgaremos su Información de identificación personal a terceros, salvo según se establece en esta Política, en la medida necesaria para prestarle un servicio solicitado, o bien en las circunstancias en que lo exija la ley. Usted acepta que, además, podemos divulgar esta información a terceros: (1) cuando tengamos razones para creer que dicha divulgación es necesaria para identificar o contactar a una persona que pueda generar perjuicios o interferencias (ya sea en forma intencional o no) para nuestros derechos o propiedad, clientes u otros usuarios de nuestro sitio, o iniciar acciones legales contra ella, o bien contra toda otra persona que pudiera verse afectada por dichas actividades; (2) para responder a procesos judiciales y brindar información a organismos de orden público, o en relación con una investigación sobre hechos relacionados con la seguridad pública, según lo permita la ley, u otro motivo que especifique la ley, como para cumplir con una citación o procedimiento legal similar.

Es posible que transfiramos su Información de identificación personal a proveedores de servicios de terceros que nos ayuden a llevar a cabo estos fines. Por ejemplo, podemos utilizar un contratista para el procesamiento de datos quien opere los sistemas informáticos en nuestra representación, para obtener soporte administrativo o técnico, u otros fines comerciales que sean necesarios para facilitarle a usted nuestras transacciones, analizar nuestros datos, prestar servicios analíticos o mantener y mejorar nuestros servicios. Siempre que se transfiera Información de identificación personal a un proveedor de servicios de terceros, este quedará vinculado contractualmente al uso de la Información de identificación personal únicamente para llevar a cabo los servicios que hemos solicitado, para cumplir con nuestra Política y para brindar la protección adecuada a esta Información de identificación personal.

Nos reservamos el derecho de transferir toda Información de identificación personal que poseamos sobre usted en caso de que nos fusionemos con otra compañía o seamos adquiridos por terceros. Es posible que divulguemos su Información de identificación personal para cualquier otro fin con su consentimiento.

#### SUS ELECCIONES PARA CONTROLAR SU INFORMACIÓN

### Cómo corregir o cambiar su información

Nos interesa la exactitud, la actualización y la integridad de la Información de identificación personal que recabamos, y tomamos las medidas necesarias para garantizar que la información que tenemos sea precisa y actual. Además de las opciones proporcionadas en esta Política, si desea revisar, enmendar, corregir, actualizar o eliminar la Información de identificación personal que hemos recopilado sobre usted por Internet, o bien dejar de recibir nuestras comunicaciones comerciales, comuníquese con nosotros a través de los siguientes medios: +1-866-376-4685 o <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>. También puede comunicarse por escrito a la siguiente dirección:

Ron Martinez  
eXperticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

Responderemos a su solicitud de acceso en el plazo legalmente estipulado o bien dentro de los 30 días. Nos reservamos el derecho de no permitir el acceso a su información si creemos, de buena fe, que dicha divulgación está prohibida por ley o si esto podría infringir los derechos de otro individuo.

Usted puede cancelar su registro en nuestro sitio o solicitar la eliminación de su Información de identificación personal de nuestro registro de visitantes enviando un mensaje de correo electrónico a [email]. Enviaremos un mensaje electrónico para confirmar la recepción de su solicitud. Después de que responda, eliminaremos la información de nuestra base de datos. La información residual puede permanecer en nuestros archivos y registros, pero no será utilizada con ningún fin comercial ni de otra naturaleza. Nos reservamos el derecho de conservar la información sobre los visitantes registrados que han infringido cualquiera de nuestras políticas o que han tenido acceso al sitio bloqueado.

### SEGURIDAD

Utilizamos una variedad de tecnologías y procesos para proteger la Información de identificación personal recabada en este sitio, incluso medidas de seguridad física, tecnológica y organizativa. Por ejemplo: utilizamos tecnología de cifrado siempre que transmitimos información personal. Desafortunadamente, ninguna tecnología de la seguridad es totalmente segura y usted debe recordar que el correo electrónico no es un medio de comunicación certero. Conservamos la Información de identificación personal que recopilamos, únicamente, mientras sea razonablemente necesario para cumplir con los fines para los cuales esta fue recabada, o bien para cumplir con cualquier exigencia legal.

Ya sea parcial o totalmente, la Información de identificación personal que recopilamos puede ser almacenada o procesada en servidores ubicados fuera de su país, incluso en los Estados Unidos, cuyas leyes sobre la protección de datos pueden diferir de aquellas del país donde usted reside. Como resultado de ello, esta información puede quedar sujeta a solicitudes de acceso de los gobiernos, tribunales u organismos de orden público en aquellas jurisdicciones, de acuerdo con las leyes de estas. De conformidad con la legislación vigente en dichas jurisdicciones, emplearemos los esfuerzos razonables para garantizar que las protecciones pertinentes estén en vigencia a fin de conservar una protección de la Información de identificación personal que sea equivalente a la otorgada por su país.

### ENLACES A OTROS SITIOS WEB

Nuestro sitio puede contener enlaces a otros sitios web de terceros. La información que comparte con un sitio de terceros no está sujeta a esta Política de privacidad. Revise la política de privacidad de todo sitio al que acceda a través de nuestro sitio web.

### PRIVACIDAD PARA MENORES

Nuestros sitios no están destinados al uso por parte de niños. A sabiendas, no recopilamos información personal de niños que sean menores de 13 años. Los niños menores de 18 años no pueden crear un perfil por Internet.

### CAMBIOS EN LA POLÍTICA

Si nuestra Política de privacidad tiene cambios, publicaremos estos cambios en nuestro sitio web con la fecha de la revisión. Lo instamos a que revise con frecuencia nuestra Política de privacidad. Su acceso continuo o el uso del sitio después de realizados dichos cambios constituye su aceptación de ellos y su acuerdo de quedar legalmente vinculado a través de esta Política, según su revisión. Si nuestras prácticas de privacidad, incluso las maneras en que usamos su Información de identificación personal, cambian materialmente desde el momento en que usted creó un perfil por Internet, le notificaremos esos cambios antes de que se implementen y le permitiremos eliminar su información como se describe arriba, en caso de que usted no esté de acuerdo con esos cambios.

### PUERTO SEGURO

eXperticity cumple con el marco legal de Puerto Seguro (Safe Harbor) de los EE. UU. y la UE que establece el Departamento de Comercio de los EE. UU. con respecto a la recopilación, el uso y la retención de datos personales de los países miembros de la Unión Europea. eXperticity ha certificado que cumple con los principios de privacidad de Puerto Seguro, a saber: aviso, elección, transferencia, seguridad, integridad de la información, acceso y exigibilidad. Para conocer más detalles sobre el programa de Puerto Seguro y consultar la certificación de eXperticity, visite <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

## POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDADE

Versão: Estados Unidos, México; África do Sul; Colômbia; Venezuela; Peru; Equador; Chile, Uruguai, Brasil; Cingapura; Filipinas; Indonésia; Malásia; Tailândia; Japão, República Popular da China; Nova Zelândia  
Data de efetivação: 10/07/2015

Essa política de privacidade descreve como a eXperticity, Inc., uma empresa localizada e incorporada nos Estados Unidos, coleta, usa e compartilha informações sobre você que são coletadas enquanto você usa o 3point5.com (“site”).

Ao usar nosso site, registrar-se em nossos serviços ou escolher enviar informações pessoais para a eXperticity por meio do site, você concorda com os termos desta Política de privacidade (“Política”). Você não precisa fornecer qualquer informação pessoal, mas se escolher não fornecer, pode ser que você não consiga acessar certas informações ou áreas do site. Se você não concordar com nenhum dos termos desta Política, não use este Site nem envie qualquer informação pessoal para a eXperticity.

Com a finalidade de identificação, é necessário pela lei local que o controlador dos dados seja eXperticity, Inc.

### QUAIS INFORMAÇÕES COLETAMOS

#### Todos os usuários

Quando você visita nosso site, coletamos informações pessoais sobre você (inclusive nome, endereço, número de telefone, endereço de e-mail, nome de usuário e senha) (“Informações de identificação pessoal”) quando você preenche formulários, comunica-se com a gente por meio do site ou cria um perfil on-line.

Também coletamos certas informações sobre seu uso de nosso site, como informações sobre seu computador, incluindo endereço IP, o tipo de navegador sendo usado e o sistema operacional do computador. Exceto se explicado o contrário nesta Política, ou conforme possa ser proibido pela lei, podemos combinar essas informações com suas informações pessoais.

#### Perfil on-line

Ao criar um perfil on-line, você pode optar por fornecer informações opcionais, como empregador, módulos de treinamento concluídos, compras feitas, fotografias, pontos ganhos etc. Quaisquer informações fornecidas no perfil estão sujeitas a esta Política. As informações que você opta por carregar ou tornar públicas do seu perfil aparecerão no site e poderão ser vistas por outros membros. Se optar por incluir informações de identificação pessoal em uma área pública do site, você consentirá na divulgação pública das informações de identificação pessoal que optar por publicar. Se não desejar publicar as informações de identificação pessoal dessa maneira, não inclua-as no material que publicar em uma área pública do site. Geralmente, fornecemos maneiras de controlar o compartilhamento do perfil e dos dados dentro do perfil no seguinte link: [www.3point5.com/action/user/account](http://www.3point5.com/action/user/account).

#### Cookies e outras tecnologias de rastreio

Nosso site também usa “cookies” (pequenos arquivos de dados armazenados no computador) e outras tecnologias de rastreio para coletar informações sobre sua visita no site. Os cookies e as outras tecnologias de rastreio que usamos não coletam informações de identificação pessoal. As informações coletadas sobre sua visita poderão ser usadas de várias maneiras, como, por exemplo, para monitorar e manter informações sobre suas visitas no nosso site, ajudar-nos a identificar e resolver problemas, melhorar o site, analisar as tendências de tráfego na Web e ajudar a proteger a segurança e integridade do site. Você pode definir o navegador para não aceitar cookies ou para notificá-lo quando receber cookies, dando a você a oportunidade de decidir aceitar ou não os cookies. Se você não aceitar cookies, ainda poderá usar o site, mas com um desempenho não tão satisfatório.

Podemos usar também tags de pixels (também conhecidas como “clear gifs”, “Web beacons” ou “1-by-1gifs”) no site. Essas tags podem ser usadas em conexão com certas páginas do site ou com mensagens de e-mail para medir a eficácia de nossas comunicações e campanhas de marketing, compilar estatísticas sobre taxas de uso e de resposta e ajudar-nos a resolver problemas que possam surgir no site.

### COMO USAMOS AS INFORMAÇÕES DE IDENTIFICAÇÃO PESSOAL COLETADAS

Podemos usar as informações de identificação pessoal coletadas com as seguintes finalidades:

  * responder às suas dúvidas e atender às suas solicitações;
  * enviar informações importantes com relação ao site, a mudanças nos termos, condições e políticas do site e/ou outras informações administrativas;
  * enviar comunicações de marketing que acreditamos ser de seu interesse e que você pode escolher não receber a qualquer momento;
  * personalizar sua navegação no site apresentando conteúdo adaptado para você;
  * permitir que você participe e se mantenha atualizado com relação aos treinamentos;
  * para nossa finalidade comercial, como análise de dados, auditorias, desenvolvimento de novos produtos, melhoria do site, melhoria dos serviços, identificação de tendências de uso e determinação da eficácia de nossas campanhas promocionais;
  * para controle de risco, cumprimento das leis e regulamentações e cumprimento de outros processos jurídicos e requisitos de aplicação da lei;
  * usar as informações sobre suas atividades no site para comunicar seu progresso aos seus empregadores e, em alguns casos, oferecer descontos de varejo;
  * para outras finalidades que serão informadas a você e as quais você consentirá ou não.

Também podemos usar as informações que recebemos sobre você do seu empregador e dos provedores de dados para nos ajudar no processamento de solicitações, na manutenção de nossos dados e na otimização de nossos serviços.

### COMPARTILHAMENTO DE SUAS INFORMAÇÕES

Não divulgaremos essas informações de identificação pessoal para terceiros, exceto conforme descrito nesta Política, a não ser que seja necessário para fornecer a você um serviço solicitado ou em circunstâncias necessárias pela lei. Você concorda que também poderemos divulgar essas informações a terceiros: (1) quando temos motivos para acreditar que essa divulgação seja necessária para identificar, entrar em contato ou entrar com ação legal contra alguém que possa estar causando lesão ou interferindo (intencional ou não intencionalmente) com nossos direitos ou propriedades, nossos clientes ou outros usuários do site ou com qualquer outra pessoa que possa ser prejudicada com essas atividades; (2) responder a processos judiciais e fornecer informações para órgãos de aplicação das leis ou em conexão com uma investigação ou problemas relacionados à segurança pública, conforme permitido pela lei, ou de alguma outra maneira, conforme exigido pela lei, como para cumprir uma intimação ou processo jurídico semelhante.

Podemos transferir suas informações de identificação pessoal para provedores de serviço terceirizados para nos ajudar a atingir esses objetivos. Por exemplo, podemos usar uma empresa terceirizada para operar sistemas de computador em nosso nome, para finalidades administrativas, de suporte técnico ou outras finalidades comerciais, conforme necessário, para facilitar nossas transações com você, analisar nossos dados, realizar serviços de análise ou manter e melhorar nossos serviços. Sempre que qualquer informação de identificação pessoal for transferida dessa maneira, para um provedor de serviços terceirizado, esse provedor será obrigado, por contrato, a usar as ferramentas de identificação pessoal apenas para realizar os serviços solicitados, em conformidade com nossa Política, e oferecer proteção adequada para as informações de identificação pessoal.

Reservamo-nos o direito de transferir qualquer informação de identificação pessoal que tivermos sobre você, no caso de nos fundir ou sermos comprados por um terceiro. Podemos divulgar suas informações de identificação pessoal para qualquer outra finalidade, com o seu consentimento.

### AS OPÇÕES DE CONTROLE DAS SUAS INFORMAÇÕES

#### Correção e alterações das suas informações

Estamos preocupados com a precisão, a atualidade e a completude das informações de identificação pessoal que coletamos e agimos de maneira adequada para garantir que as informações que temos sejam precisas e atualizadas. Além disso, com relação às opções fornecidas nesta política, se você desejar revisar, corrigir, atualizar, excluir as informações de identificação pessoal que coletamos sobre você on-line ou se não quiser mais receber nossas comunicações de marketing, entre em contato conosco em: +1-866-376-4685 ou <http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback>. Também é possível entrar em contato conosco escrevendo para:

Ron Martinez  
eXperticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

Responderemos à sua solicitação de acesso durante qualquer período de tempo exigido pela lei ou no prazo de 30 dias. Temos também o direito de não permitir acesso às suas informações se acreditarmos, de boa fé, que essa divulgação é proibida por lei ou se os direitos de outro indivíduo estiverem sendo violados.

Você pode cancelar o registro no site e/ou solicitar a remoção de suas informações de identificação pessoal dos nossos registros de visitantes enviando um e-mail em http://www.3point5.com/feedback. Enviaremos um e-mail para confirmar a solicitação. Depois que você responder, removeremos as informações do banco de dados. Informações residuais poderão permanecer em nossos arquivos e em nossos registros, mas elas não serão usadas com qualquer finalidade, seja comercialmente ou qualquer outra. Temos o direito de manter as informações sobre visitantes registrados que tenham violado qualquer uma de nossas políticas ou que tenham tido o acesso ao site bloqueado.

#### SEGURANÇA

Usamos uma variedade de tecnologias e processos para proteger as informações de identificação pessoal coletadas no site, incluindo medidas de segurança física, tecnológica e organizacional. Por exemplo, usamos tecnologia de criptografia sempre que vamos transmitir alguma informação pessoal. Infelizmente, nenhuma tecnologia de segurança é completamente segura e é necessário lembrar que o e-mail não é um meio seguro de comunicação. As informações de identificação pessoal que coletamos são mantidas no site durante o tempo razoavelmente necessário para atender às finalidades para as quais elas foram coletadas ou para atender a quaisquer requisitos legais.

Algumas ou todas as informações de identificação pessoal que coletamos podem ser armazenadas ou processadas em servidores localizados fora do seu país, inclusive nos Estados Unidos, cujas leis de proteção dos dados podem diferir das leis do país em que você mora. Como resultado, essas informações poderão estar sujeitas a solicitações de acesso de governos, tribunais ou de outros órgãos de aplicação das leis nessas jurisdições, de acordo com as leis dessas jurisdições. Sujeitos às leis aplicáveis nessas outras jurisdições, usaremos os esforços possíveis e razoáveis para garantir que as proteções adequadas existam para manter as proteções das informações de identificação pessoal que sejam equivalentes às do seu país.

#### LINKS PARA OUTROS SITES

Nosso site pode conter links para sites de propriedade de terceiros. As informações que você compartilha com um site de terceiros não estão sujeitas a esta política de privacidade. Analise a política de privacidade de qualquer site que acessar pelo nosso site.

Nossos sites não devem ser usados por crianças. Não coletamos, conscientemente, informações pessoais de crianças menores de 13 anos. As crianças menores de 18 anos são proibidas de criar um perfil on-line.

#### ALTERAÇÕES DA POLÍTICA

Se nossa política de privacidade for alterada, publicaremos essas alterações no site com a data da revisão. Incentivamos os usuários a analisar nossa política de privacidade periodicamente. Seu acesso e/ou uso contínuo do site depois de qualquer uma dessas alterações constitui a aceitação e concordância de estar legalmente vinculado a esta política, conforme revisada. Se nossas práticas de privacidade, incluindo as maneiras como usamos as informações de identificação pessoal, tiverem sido materialmente alteradas com relação ao momento em que você criou um perfil on-line, nós o notificaremos sobre essas alterações, antes que elas entrem em vigor, e permitiremos que você exclua essas informações, conforme descrito acima, se discordar delas.

#### SAFE HARBOR

A eXperticity está de acordo com a estrutura Safe Harbor (Porto seguro) da UE e dos EUA, conforme definido pelo Departamento de comércio dos EUA, com relação à coleta, uso e retenção de dados pessoais de países-membros da União Europeia. A eXperticity garante que adota os princípios de privacidade Safe Harbor de aviso, escolha, transferência para terceiros, segurança, integridade, acesso e aplicação dos dados. Para saber mais sobre o programa Safe Harbor e ver a certificação da eXperticity, visite <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

## プライバシーポリシー

バージョン：米国、メキシコ、南アフリカ、コロンビア、ベネズエラ、ペルー、エクアドル、チリ、ウルグアイ、ブラジ ル、シンガポール、フィリピン、インドネシア、マレーシア、タイ、日本、中華人民共和国、ニュージーランド向け草稿 発効日： 10/07/2015

本プライバシーポリシーは、米国に所在し登記されている企業eXperticity, Incが、ユーザーが 3point5.com（以下、「サイト」）を利用中に記録されるユーザー情報を、どのように収集、使用、共有するかについて説明するものです。

当  
社サイトを利用すること、当社サービスに登録すること、またはサイト経由で個人情報をeXperticityに送信することを選択することによって、ユー  
ザーは本プライバシーポリシー（以下、「ポリシー」）の条件に同意するものとします。 ユーザーは、いかなる個人情報も提出する必要はありませ  
ん。しかし個人情報を提出しないことを選択すると、サイトの特定の情報または領域にアクセスすることができない場合があります。 本ポリシーの  
いずれの条件に同意しない場合も、本サイトの利用、またはeXperticityへの個人情報の送信を中止してください。

現地法で本人確認が義務付けられている範囲で、データ管理者はeXperticity, Incです。

### 当社が収集する情報

#### すべてのユーザー

ユーザーが当社サイトにアクセスする場合、ユーザーが当社のフォームに記入する時、当社サイト経由で当社と連絡を取る時、またはオンラインプロフィールを  
作成する時に、当社はユーザーに関する個人情報（氏名、住所、電話番号、電子メールアドレス、ユーザー名、パスワードなど）を収集します（以 下、「個人  
識別情報」）。

また、当社は、IPアドレス、使用しているブラウザーの種類、コンピューターのオペレーティングシステム  
を含むユーザーのコンピューターに関する情報など、当社サイトの利用に関する特定の情報を収集します。 本ポリシーで別途説明されている場合、  
または法律で禁止されている可能性がある場合を除き、当社は当該情報をユーザーの個人情報と結合させることがあります。 オンラインプロフィール  
ユーザーがオンラインプロフィールを作成する場合、ユーザーは、雇用主、修了済みトレーニングモジュール、購入状況、写真、獲得ポイントなどの任意の情報  
を提供することを選択できます。 ユーザーが自分のプロフィールに記載する情報は、本ポリシーの対象となります。 ユーザーがアップ  
ロードまたは公開することを選択する情報はユーザーのプロフィールであり、サイトに表示され、かつ、ほかの会員が閲覧する可能性があります。  
ユーザーが、サイトの公開領域に個人識別情報を掲載することを選択する場合、ユーザーは、その選択により投稿する個人識別情報の公開に同意するものとしま  
す。 このような形で自らの個人識別情報を公開することをユーザーが希望しない場合は、サイトの公開領域に投稿するデータに当該の個人識別情報  
を含めないでください。 当社は、リンク先（www.3point5.com/action/user/account）にて、一般的なユー  
ザープロフィール共有の管理方法、およびユーザープロフィール内のデータの管理方法を提示しています。

### クッキーなどのトラッキング技術

当  
社サイトでは、当社サイトへのユーザーアクセスに関する情報を収集するために、「クッキー（Cookie）」（ユーザーのコンピューターに保存される小さ  
なファイル）などのトラッキング技術も使用します。 当社が使用するクッキーおよびトラッキング技術は、個人識別情報を記録しません。  
ユーザーアクセスに関して記録される情報は、当社サイトへのユーザーアクセスに関する情報の監視や保持、問題の特定や対処、当社サイトの改  
良、Webトラフィック傾向の分析、および当社サイトの安全性や完全性の保護のためなど、さまざまな方法で使用される可能性があります。 ユー  
ザーは、各自が使用するブラウザーがクッキーを受け入れないように、またはクッキーを受信した時に通知するように設定することができるので、クッキー受け  
入れの可否を判断することができます。 クッキーを受け入れなくてもユーザーは当社サイトを利用することは可能ですが、機能が制限される場合が  
あります。

また、当社は、ピクセルタグ（別称：「クリアgif」、「ウェブビーコン」、「ワンバイワンgif」）も、当社  
サイトで使用することがあります。 場合によって、これらを当社サイトの特定のページまたは電子メールメッセージと関連させて使用し、当社の広  
報およびマーケティングキャンペーンの効果を測定したり、利用率および応答率に関する統計値を編集したり、当社サイト上で生じる可能性のある問題の解決を  
助けたりします。

#### 収集した個人識別情報の使用方法

当社は、以下の目的で収集する個人識別情報を使用することがあります。

  * ユーザーの問い合わせに対応するため、およびユーザーの要請を満たすため
  * 当社サイト、条件・条項・ポリシーの変更や、その他の管理情報に関する重要な情報をユーザーに送信するため
  * ユーザーが関心を持つと思われるマーケティング情報（随時配信停止可能）をユーザーに送信するため
  * ユーザーに合わせたコンテンツを表示することによって、当社サイトの機能をパーソナライズするため
  * ユーザーがトレーニングを記録できるようにするため
  * データの分析、監視、新製品開発、サイトの拡充、サービスの改善、利用傾向の特定、プロモーションキャンペーンの効果の判断といった当社事業目的のため
  * リスク管理、法規制の遵守、ならびに、その他訴訟手続および法的処置の要件を遵守するため
  * サイト上のユーザー行動情報を使用して、進捗状況を雇用主に伝えたり、場合によっては小売割引をユーザーに提供したりするため
  * ユーザーに告知され、かつ、ユーザーが同意するその他の目的のため

当社はまた、ユーザーの雇用主、およびリクエストの処理、当社データの保持やサービスの最適化において当社をサポートする情報提供業者から受け取るユーザー情報も使用することがあります。

#### ユーザー情報の共有

本ポリシーの記載に基づき依頼されたサービスをユーザーに提供するために必要な範囲で、または法律で要請される一定の状況を除き、当社はユーザーの個人識  
別情報を第三者に開示しません。 ユーザーは、以下のような場合にも、当社がこの情報を第三者に開示する可能性もあることに同意するものとしま  
す： (1) 当社の権利もしくは財産、当社サイトの顧客もしくはその他ユーザー、または後述の行動によって害を被る可能性のある者  
に、（故意または過失により）害を及ぼしたり、妨害したりする可能性のある者を特定するため、前述の者に連絡を取るため、または前述の者に対して訴訟を起  
こすために、当該情報の開示が必要であると当社が確信する理由がある場合、(2) 訴訟手続に応じ、法執行機関に情報を提供する場合、または召  
喚令状もしくは類似の法的措置に従うためなど、法律で認められているとおり、または別途法律の定めるところにより、公衆安全に関わる問題の調査に関連する  
場合。

当社は、これらの目的を達成できるように当社を支援する第三者のサービス提供業者に、ユーザーの個人識別情報を転送  
することがあります。 たとえば、当社は、当社とユーザーとのやりとり、データの分析、分析サービスの実行を円滑化するために必要に応じて、管  
理上、技術サポート上またはその他事業上の目的で、当社に代わってコンピューターシステムを操作するデータ処理請負業者を利用することがあります。  
そのような第三者サービス提供業者に個人識別情報が転送される場合、当該業者は、当社が依頼したサービスの実行のためにのみ個人識別情報を使  
用し、当社ポリシーを遵守し、さらに個人識別情報の適切な保護することが契約上の拘束事項となります。

当社が第三者と合併するとき、または当社が第三者に買収されるとき、当社は、ユーザーについて当社が保有する個人識別情報を譲渡する権利を留保します。 当社は、ユーザーの同意を得て、その他の目的でユーザーの個人識別情報を開示することがあります。

### 個人情報管理に関するユーザーの選択

#### 個人情報の修正または変更

当  
社は、当社が収集する個人識別情報の正確性、最新性、完全性に配慮しており、かつ、当社が保有する情報が正確で最新のものであることを確実にするため、適  
切な手順を講じています。 本ポリシーでユーザーに提示されている選択肢に加えて、当社がインターネット上で収集したユーザーに関する個人識別  
情報の見直し、修正、更新、削除を希望する場合、または当社マーケティング情報メールの受信停止を希望する場合は、  
+1-866-376-4685または<http://www.3point5.com/action/feedback> にて、当社までご連絡ください。 または、下記宛てに文書でご連絡ください。

Ron Martinez  
eXperticity  
9 Exchange Plaza, Suite 1000  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111

当  
社は、法律上義務付けられている期間内、または30日以内に、ユーザーのアクセス要請に対応いたします。 当社は、当該の開示が法律で禁止され  
ている、または他の個人の権利を侵害する可能性があることを善意で確信する場合、ユーザー情報へのアクセスを許可しない権利を留保します。 ユーザー  
は、[email]宛てに電子メールを送信することによって、当社サイトへの登録を取り消すことや、当社訪問者記録から自らの個人識別情報を削除するよう  
依頼することができます。 当社は、ユーザーの依頼を確認するために電子メールを送信します。 ユーザーが返答した後に、ユーザー情  
報をデータベースから削除します。 残留情報が当社のアーカイブおよび記録に残る場合がありますが、当該情報は商業上またはその他のいかなる目  
的にも使用されません。 当社は、当社ポリシーに違反したことのある登録済み訪問者、またはブロックされたサイトにアクセスしたことのある登録  
済み訪問者の情報を保持する権利を留保します。 セキュリティ

物理的、技術的、組織的なセキュリティ対策など、当社は、本  
サイトで収集された個人識別情報を保護するために、さまざまな技術および手順を用いています。 たとえば、当社では個人情報を送信する時は、常  
に暗号化技術を使用しています。 残念ながら、完全に安全なセキュリティ技術は存在しません。そして、電子メールが安全な通信手段ではないこと  
を忘れてはいけません。 当社は、個人識別情報の収集目的を果たすため、または法的要件を満たすために合理的に必要とされる期間のみ、収集した  
個人識別情報を保持します。

当社が収集する個人識別情報の一部または全部は、米国など、あなたの国。以外の場所にあるサー  
バーで保管または処理されることがあり、そこのデータ保護法は、ユーザーの居住国のものとは異なる可能性があります。 そのため、当該情報は、  
各管轄権における法に従って、各管轄権の政府、裁判所または法執行機関からのアクセス要請の対象となることがあります。 当社は、そのような、  
その他の管轄権における適用法に基づき、あなたの国。において個人識別情報に相当する情報の保護を維持するために適切な保護が行なわれるよう妥当な努力を  
払います。

### 他のWebサイトへのリンク

当社サイトには、第三者が所有するWebサイト  
へのリンクが含まれていることがあります。 ユーザーが第三者サイトと共有する情報は、本プライバシーポリシーの対象ではありません。  
当社サイト経由でアクセスするサイトのプライバシーポリシーをご確認ください。

### 子どものプライバシー

当社サイトは、子供用ではありません。 当社が13歳未満の子供の個人情報を故意に収集することはありません。 18歳未満の子供は、オンラインプロフィールを作成することを禁じられています。

### ポリシーの変更

プ  
ライバシーポリシーを変更する場合、当社は、改訂日と共に、変更点を当社Webサイトに掲載します。 当社プライバシーポリシーを定期的に確認  
することをお勧めします。 ユーザーは、当該変更後に継続的にサイトにアクセスする場合やサイトを利用する場合、改定済みの本ポリシーによって  
法的に拘束されることを承諾し、かつ同意したものとみなされます。 オンラインプロフィールをユーザーが作成した後、当社の個人識別情報取り扱  
い方法を含めて当社のプライバシー慣行が大きく変更された場合には、当社は、当該変更点が発効する前に変更点についてユーザーに通知し、かつユーザーが変  
更に同意しない場合には、上述のとおりユーザーが自分の情報を削除できるようにします。

### セーフハーバー

eXperticity  
は、EU加盟国からの個人情報の収集、使用および保持に関しては、米国商務省が定める米国欧州間セーフハーバーフレームワーク（U.S.-  
EU Safe Harbor Framework）に準拠します。 eXperticityは、通知、選択、転送、セ  
キュリティ、データの完全性、アクセスおよび実施におけるセーフハーバープライバシー原則（Safe Harbor  
Privacy Principles）に準拠していることを証明しています。 セーフハーバープログラムの詳細について、および  
eXperticityの証明書の閲覧については、  http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/をご覧ください。
